<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musical Strucuture</string>
    <string name="playlists">Playlists</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="songs">Songs</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="artist">Artist</string>
    <string name="album">Album</string>
    <string name="playingSong">Name of the song - Name of the artist</string>
    <string name="homeExplanation">This activity is the home screen you lend when you open the app,
        you have a navigation bar to access to all activities. You can click on each
        icon to access to a new activity. At the bottom, a little player in a card view showing the current song which is playing.There are
        3  icon buttons at this player, play, next song, previous song. There will be other cards views to show on top of the player,
        the recommended songs for the user, his favorite playlist/album/artist.etc.</string>
    <string name="playlistExplanation">This activity shows all playlists the user makes. You can access to all activities from the navigation bar,
        there is also the little player at the bottom.
        There will be a navigation menu to browse other kind of playlists, the user could click on the playlit\'s name and it will start in the player.</string>
    <string name="libraryExplanation"> This activity shows the songs library, you could filter or sort the songs by genres, artists and by albums.
    There will have checkboxes next the name of the song/artist/album/genre to be selected to create a new playlist or add into an existing playlist.
    the user will just have to click on the song/artist/album/genre or the checkboxed selection to start playing the song/artist/album/genre.</string>
    <string name="searchExplanation"> This activity shows a search field where the user can search a song/artist/album/genre.
        Like is in library activity, the user can select the found song/artist/album/genre with a checkbox next to it, and create a playlist, or add to an existing playlist.
    The user could also directly click on the found song/artist/album/genre and it will start on the player.</string>
</resources>
